
var questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which prototype is used when we are developing web applications?",
        answer: "Extreme",
        options: [
            "Throw away",
            "Incremental",
            "Extreme",
            "Evolutionary",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Waterfall model is also called as?",
        answer: "Conventional Software Development Model",
        options: [
            "Iterative Incremental",
            "Conventional Software Development Model",
            "Incremental iteratve model",
            "Waterflow model",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "CMMI is developed by?",
        answer: "Software Engineering Institute",
        options: [
            "Software Engineering Institute",
            "Brunel Institute,London",
            "Suhail Institute Of Technology,UK",
            "Niloy International College, Canada",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following are integrity constraints?",
        answer: "Both A & C",
        options: [
            "Primary key",
            "Super key",
            "Unique",
            "Both A & C",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "DBMS stands for",
        answer: "Data Base Management System",
        options: [
            "Data Bound Management System",
            "Data Base Management System",
            "Data Base Manipulation System",
            "None of the above",
        ],
    },
   {
        numb: 6,
        question: "The expression x=4+2%-8 evaluates to?",
        answer: "6",
        options: [
            "-6",
            "6",
            "4",
            "-4",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 7,
        question: 'int x=1,y=2,*p;p=*&x;y= *p;What will be the value of y after the execution of above code?',
        answer: "1",
        options: [
            "2",
            "1",
            "1234",
            "1111",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 8,
        question: "In C++,_______ creates object, eventhough it was not defined in class?",
        answer: "Implicit Constructor",
        options: [
            "Default Constructor",
            "Paramaterized Constructor",
            "Copy Constructor",
            "Implicit Constructor",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 9,
        question: "In _______ inheritence, the constructors are executed in the order of inheritence?",
        answer: "Multilevel",
        options: [
            "Multiple",
            "Multipath",
            "Multilevel",
            "Hierarchial",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 10,
        question: "Evaluate the Java expression, if x=3,y=5 and z=10",
        answer: "24",
        options: [
            "24",
            "23",
            "20",
            "21",
        ],
    },
];